The first change would almost certainly reduce the number of pageviews needed.
我们几乎可以肯定第一种更改能够减少所需的页面查看量
By changing the unit of diversion to be the same as the unit of analysis,
通过根据分析单元更改分组单元
the variability of the metric will probably decrease and
指标差异性很可能会降低
be closer to the analytical estimate.
并更贴近分析估计
By decreasing the variability of the metric,
降低指标差异性
you decrease the number of pageviews you need to be confident in your results.
就能减少获得可靠结果所需的页面查看量
The main question here is whether the less consistent experience will be
这一更改的主要问题在于
acceptable.
其对用户体验一致性的影响是否可以接受
In this case, if audacity recalculated the empirical estimate of the standard
在这个例子中 如果优达学城使用页面查看作为分组单元
error using the pageview as the unit of diversion, they might find
来重新计算标准误差的经验估计量
that the new standard error was 0.0209 for the same sample size.
那么他们就会发现相同样本量的新标准误差是 0.0209
Then only 34,000 pageviews per group would be necessary,
这样 每组 34,000 次页面查看就够了
which is quite an improvement.
这个减少幅度很可观
Targeting the experiment to English traffic will also reduce the total
将实验目标设定为仅英语用户产生的流量
number of pageviews needed.
也有助于减少所需的总页面查看量
Since the non-English traffic is not effected,
因为非英语用户产生的流量不受影响
including it will dilute the results of the experiment,
纳入它将会稀释实验结果
which would increase the number of pageviews needed.
从而导致所需的页面查看量增加
Of course,
当然
there are fewer non-English page views available than total page views.
可用的非英语用户产生的页面查看量较总页面查看量要少
So this might not reduce the time frame of the experiment,
这可能不会缩短实验所需的时间范围
but other experiments could be run on the non-English traffic in the meantime.
但它允许我们同时对非英语用户产生的流量开展其他实验
So this could still be worth doing.
所以这一更改也值得尝试
Filtering the traffic could also impact your choice of practical significance
筛选流量还可能影响你对实际显著性界线的
boundary.
选择
First, since you're only looking at a subset of your traffic,
首先 因为你观察的是总流量的一个子集
you might need a bigger change before it matters to the business.
你可能需要做出较大更改 然后才能对业务产生影响
Or since your variability is probably lower,
或者 因为你的差异性可能较低
you might want to take advantage of that and
你可能想利用这个优势
detect smaller changes rather than decreasing the size of the experiment.
来检测较小更改 而不是减少实验规模
Because the practical significance boundary could move in either direction,
因为实际显著性界线可能向任意方向移动
your size could really move in either direction.
你的规模也可能如此
But it's likely that the variance will go down and the practical significance
但是因为方差可能下降 而实际显著性界线可能上升
boundary will increase, so it's likely that the size will be smaller.
所以 实际所需规模可能会更小
In this case, suppose that audacity keeps pageviews as the unit of diversion
在这个例子中 假设优达学城继续使用页面查看作为分组单元
and then targeting the experiment to English only traffic further
然后将实验目标设定为仅英语用户产生的流量
reduces the standard error to 0.0188.
以此进一步将标准误差降低至 0.0188
And they also decide to increase their practical significance boundary to 0.015
他们还决定将英语用户产生的流量的实际显著性界线
for the English traffic only.
增加至 0.015
At this point, they would only need 12,000 pageviews per group.
这样的话 他们只需要获得每组 12,000 次页面查看即可
The third change, changing the metric, depends on the specific definition.
第三种更改是根据具体定义更改指标
But it will often not make a significant difference to the variability,
它通常不会导致差异性发生重大变化
especially if you're using a short time window for the probability.
特别是在使用短期时间范围来分析概率时
If there is a difference, the variability will probably go down.
如果产生了差异 那么差异性可能会下降
Since the unit of analysis would be the same as the unit of diversion in
因为在这个例子中 分析单元与分组单元
this case.
相同
So this could reduce the number of pageviews needed, but
它可能有助于减少所需的页面查看量
it also might not help much.
但效果可能有限
Again, I did these two sizing calculations with
为了满足某些人的好奇心 我顺便解释一下
code linked in the Instructor's Notes, if you're curious.
在计算这两个规模数据时 我使用的就是讲师备注中链接的 r 代码